Big Blue, let's welcome JC Davis,
offensive lineman out of Illinois, with
the sixth round, 192nd
pick. JC, when you heard that, what's
the first thing that popped up in your
head when you heard your name called?
I knew I knew coach Harbaugh told me he
was going to come get me, so when I got
that call, I was super excited. I was
ready to go.
>> All right, John Harbaugh, man of his
word. Let's go even deeper into what
that original conversation was like. You
know, don't give us anything, we're
going to leak to TMZ or anything, but
what was what was that conversation like
with the Giants and coach Harbaugh? I
felt like me and coach Harbaugh, we
talked a little ball, but we mostly
talked about like a little bit of stuff
like outside of the field. Like just
just she's trying to see who I was as a
person, my character.
All right. Well, what what how are you?
What how how are you as a person? How
are you as a character?
I mean, I'm I'm quiet unless you know
me. Like but I talk to people, but like
other than that, like I'm cool, I'm
chill. Like I'm not doing too much
extra. I'm just I'm just working. All
right, so let's talk some football, man.
I always ask guys like what's your why?
You know, when we talk about the dog
days of camp, things getting things
getting hard, what's going to keep JC
Davis going?
My family. My mom and dad sacrificed so
much for me to get to where I'm at right
now today. Like it'll be it'll be like a
dishonor if I don't put my all into it.
Like when I'm feeling when I'm feeling
down, fatigue, all of that.
You got a quite the journey, man. Like
you started as a defensive lineman, you
played that throughout the course of
high school, then you switch over to
O-line at Contra Costa College, and then
you master it at Illinois, all Big Ten,
you got a high PFF grade. What was the
biggest thing or the biggest challenge
on that switch? And when we come to
putting in our 10,000 hours, like talk
about the grind, man.
I feel like I always played both sides
in high school, so I played offense and
defense. So like and I always played
like tackle and guard or whatever, so
like it wasn't too much of a a challenge
for me. I'll just say like going into
college and just like learning like cuz
I I transferred like two two times cuz I
had to go from Juco to New Mexico, New
Mexico to Illinois. So I just learning
like to uh the new schemes and the new
coaches. Like just understanding the
coaches' languages and how they how they
speak and stuff like that. I can say
that.
49 consecutive starts, that's Iron Man
status right there right there, bro.
Like you're durable. Kind of talk about
what that was like. Like to be able to
play in 49 straight games and be a guy
that your teammates can rely on.
Just make sure you take care of your
body. Like I feel like that was like the
biggest part is taking care of my body,
make sure my body is right, my mind is
right to play the game. Cuz like if your
body your mind not right to play the
game, then you're not going to be all in
it. So I feel like that was like the big
part of my 49 starts.
>> you're going to get a chance to to block
for Jackson Dart going in his second
year. You know Jackson, you what you
what do you know about him and how
excited are you to to come in the to the
facility and meet him for the first time
and get after it?
>> Oh, I'm I'm I'm super excited to meet
him. I've seen some stuff on social
media. He seems like a great a great
person and a great quarterback you want
to block for, you want to play for, put
your all in for. So so yeah. Lastly, the
fifth pick of the draft, Arvell Reese
from The Ohio State University. Can you
guys no bad blood now that you guys are
on the same team, right? No bad blood at
all, nah.
We had a we had a good game out there.
We was going at it. All right.
>> Putting in work. All right, man. Well,
congratulations and uh we look forward
to getting you in the building here
pretty soon, bro. And thank you for
having me on, man.